{
    "quiz": [
      {
        "question": "Who is the main protagonist of the Naruto series?",
        "answers": ["Sasuke", "Naruto", "Kakashi", "Sakura"],
        "correctAnswer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of Naruto's father?",
        "answers": ["Jiraiya", "Minato", "Orochimaru", "Hiruzen"],
        "correctAnswer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of Naruto's mother?",
        "answers": ["Kushina", "Mikoto", "Tsunade", "Inoichi"],
        "correctAnswer": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the Nine-Tailed Fox that attacked Konoha?",
        "answers": ["Kurama", "Isobu", "Matatabi", "Gyuki"],
        "correctAnswer": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of Naruto's signature technique?",
        "answers": [
          "Rasengan",
          "Chidori",
          "Fireball Jutsu",
          "Shadow Clone Jutsu"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the Hidden Village where Naruto lives?",
        "answers": ["Sunagakure", "Konohagakure", "Kirigakure", "Iwagakure"],
        "correctAnswer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the first Hokage of Konoha?",
        "answers": [
          "Tobirama Senju",
          "Hashirama Senju",
          "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
          "Danzo Shimura"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the second Hokage of Konoha?",
        "answers": [
          "Tobirama Senju",
          "Hashirama Senju",
          "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
          "Danzo Shimura"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the third Hokage of Konoha?",
        "answers": [
          "Tobirama Senju",
          "Hashirama Senju",
          "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
          "Danzo Shimura"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the current Hokage of Konoha?",
        "answers": [
          "Kakashi Hatake",
          "Tsunade Senju",
          "Naruto Uzumaki",
          "Shikamaru Nara"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
      }
    ]
}